(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
がうる・ぐら Gawr Gura 3D LIVE
Gawr Gura 3D LIVE
Whoa!
REFLECT (Jazz ver.)
Artist: Gawr Gura
水面に映る自分がいた
I saw myself reflected on the water's surface.
あぁ私は悪いサメです
Ah, I am a bad shark.
ずっと逸らしていた
I had been averting my eyes.
赤く光るその目
Those red glowing eyes.
海の底暗闇に消えていく
Disappearing into the darkness at the bottom of the sea.
どうして泣くのよ
Why are you crying?
欲しいものなら全部手に入れた
I got everything I wanted.
教えて私は
Tell me, did I...
望んでいた私になれたかな
...become the person I wanted to be?
嘘はつかないでも本当じゃない
I don't lie, but it's not the truth either.
本音は言わない他愛もない
I don't say my true feelings, it's just trivial talk.
いつかはどこかで
Someday, somewhere...
分かり合える時が来るの
...will the time come when we can understand each other?
ずっと追い求めた
I've always searched for it.
私なりの答え
My own answer.
自分には嘘つきたくない
I don't want to lie to myself.
REFLECT (Jazz ver.)
Smile...
ごめんね
Sorry...
今まで
Until now...
気づかなかったことがあるんだけど
こうして
There are things I hadn't noticed, but
in this way,
あなたがいてくれたから今の私はいる
because you were here for me, I am who I am now.
過去は消えない そんなことはない
"The past doesn't disappear," that's not true.
未来は見えない おこがましいじゃない
"The future can't be seen," isn't that presumptuous?
ここから 静かに私を見守っていてね
From here, please quietly keep watching over me.
さよなら ありがとう
Goodbye, thank you.
隠していた私はもういない
The me I was hiding is no longer here.
さよなら ありがとう
Goodbye, thank you.
全て受け入れて生きていくから
Because I will live on, accepting everything.
海の底はつまらないけど
The bottom of the sea is boring, but...
あなたのことは見つめているから
because I'm watching over you...
いつでも どこでも 私らしく生きていこう
Anytime, anywhere, let's live true to ourselves.
Thrilling! Is this love?
Artist: ERI-na (Canary Club)
Composer: TSUNKU / Lyrics: TSUNKU
ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
ねえ 歌うわ
Hey, I'm going to sing!
そうよ あなたに
Yes, for you.
あまちょいけれど 恥ずかしいかもね
It's a bit sweet, but it might be embarrassing.
かーもね! ハイ!
Might be! Yes!
願い事の呪文
A spell for my wish.
ほら むにゃむにゃむにゃ
Look, mumble mumble mumble.
ハイ! ハイ! ハイ!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
ずっとこのまま時が止まるかもね
Time might stop just like this forever.
かーもね! ハイ!
Might be! Yes!
こういうのが恋なの? ドキドキドーン!
Is this what love is? Heart pounding boom!
ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
しかもね かーもね! かーもね! ハイ!
And also, might be! Might be! Yes!
スキスキスキ
Love love love!
ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
昨日よりも...かもね かーもね! ハイ!
Even more than yesterday, maybe! Maybe! Yes!
ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
ねえ 歌って
Hey, sing!
そうよ あなたも
Yes, you too.
乙女の気持ちが伝わるといいな
I hope a maiden's feelings get through.
いーいな! ハイ!
That would be nice! Yes!
のどから出そうなくらい もうラブラブラブ
So much it's about to come out of my throat, already love love love!
ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
ずっとこのままあなた素敵がいいな
I hope you stay wonderful like this forever.
いーいな! ハイ!
That would be nice! Yes!
こういうのははじめて ドキドキドーン!
This is the first time, heart pounding boom!
ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
ああ いいな いーいな! ハイ!
Ah, it's nice! It's nice! Yes!
スキスキスキ
Love love love!
ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
さっきよりも...いいな いーいな! ハイ!
Even more than a moment ago, it's nice! It's nice! Yes!
ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Hoi! Welcome to the Goomba's official first ever 3D live concert!
Yay! Ah, okay.
I have a lot to show you today.
Oh, and we have a lot of guests to sing with as well.
So, I'm going to need you to stand up and let's get this party started! Woo!
日本のファンも来てくれてありがとうございます。
いつもサポートしてくれるのが嬉しいです。
Thank you to the Japanese fans for coming.
It makes me happy that you always support me.
Hmm, first to the stage for the first time ever, Reflect jazz flavor. My first song ever.
I wanted to give it a special new touch just for you.
Um, it's a little different from the original, but...
I really like it. Jazzified.
Maybe I'm biased, so...
...but I hope you enjoyed it regardless.
How do you like the stage though?
みて、みて! Look!
Look, look! Look!
Look at this ebi over here. Looking suave, I know?
Look at this shrimp over here. Looking suave, I know?
Oh, and how many fish can you spot, hmm?
There's quite a few. There's, uh, Royal Blue Tang, and then there's Yellow Tang...
...and I'm sure, I'm sure you guys know all about your fish, right? All your fishes. Of course you do.
I gotta say though, all this dancing is making me hungry.
And all this fish talk is making me, hmm, hungry-mungry.
I guess it's time for guest then, no?
いくよ!
Here we go!
MOGU MOGU YUMMY!
Artist: Nekomata Okayu
森羅万象の 悪戦苦闘も
Even the struggles of all creation
マヨネーズかけたら大体美味しくなる
Will mostly taste good if you put mayonnaise on them
君が泣いても お腹は空くよ
Even if you cry, I'll still get hungry
消極的だった ごめん ごめん
I was being passive, sorry, sorry
酸いも甘いも 勝手に食べて
Eating both the sour and the sweet as I please
ご迷惑おかけしています
I'm sorry for being a nuisance
毒気を抜いて 変な味のジュース
Draining the malice from this weird-tasting juice
心を無にして 飲み込みます
Emptying my mind as I swallow it down
嗚呼 混沌情報のレストランで
Ah, in this restaurant of chaotic information
嘘っぱちのメニューにお茶こぼして
Spilling tea over the fake menu
君ともぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munching along with you, munching
銃撃戦の真ん中でもぐもぐ (Yeah!)
Munching in the middle of a gunfight (Yeah!)
魑魅魍魎 ハラペコの群れ
Monsters and spirits, a starving crowd
満腹になる未来を願っているよ
I'm wishing for a future where we're full
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munching, munching
世界が終わる前にもぐもぐヤミー
Before the world ends, Mogu Mogu Yummy
マジ神
Seriously divine
やむやむ ありのまんま もぐもぐヤミー
Yum yum, just as it is, Mogu Mogu Yummy
マジ神
Seriously divine
Magic Coming
この世を味わうんだ うまうま
Savoring this world, so tasty
離散のミルフィーユサンド
A mille-feuille sandwich of dispersion
不適当のオーロラソース
Inappropriate Aurora sauce
大雑把な味付け お目見えだよ
Roughly seasoned, here it is
美味しくなったら OK OK
If it tastes good, then OK OK
良いも悪いも いっぱい食べて
Eating lots of both the good and the bad
汚れた口元 拭います
Wiping my dirty mouth
おにぎり ピザ ケーキ 豪華なフルコース
Rice balls, pizza, cake, a lavish full course
罠を謳歌 吐き気を堪えます
Enjoying the trap, holding back the nausea
嗚呼 妄想流言飛語のバイキングで
Ah, in this buffet of delusions and rumors
毒入りと絶品料理 選び分けて
Distinguishing the poison from the delicacies
君ともぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munching along with you, munching
デスゲームの教室でもぐもぐ (Yeah!)
Munching in a death game classroom (Yeah!)
魑魅魍魎 ハラペコの群れ
Monsters and spirits, a starving crowd
仲の良い君と生き残れたらいいな
I hope I can survive with you, my good friend
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munching, munching
数年後もこの場所で もぐもぐヤミー
In this place even years from now, Mogu Mogu Yummy
マジ神 今夜の晩御飯は もぐもぐヤミー
Seriously divine, tonight's dinner is Mogu Mogu Yummy
マジ神
Seriously divine
Magic Coming
次はお前の番だ もぐもぐヤミー マジ神
Next is your turn, Mogu Mogu Yummy, seriously divine
マジ神 やむやむ ありのまんま
Seriously divine, yum yum, just as it is
もぐもぐヤミー マジ神
Mogu Mogu Yummy, seriously divine
Magic Coming
この世を味わうんだ うまうま
Savoring this world, so tasty
うー せーの!
Woo, one, two!
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munching, munching, munching, munching, munching, munching
もぐもぐヤミー
Mogu Mogu Yummy
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munching, munching, munching, munching, munching, munching
もぐもぐヤミー
Mogu Mogu Yummy
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munching, munching, munching, munching, munching, munching
もぐもぐヤミー
Mogu Mogu Yummy
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munching, munching, munching, munching, munching, munching
もぐもぐヤミー やみい
Mogu Mogu Yummy, yummy
Okayu-senpai!
Thank you for singing with me!
This is a dream come true.
I could cry right now.
Gura!
I am so happy too.
Thank you.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
Huh? What?
At home, I have three monitors, and they are all Gura!
Gura Wo-Paper!
Hey, really? That makes me so happy!
Yes, I am a big Gura otaku.
What?! I'm an Okayu otaku too!
相思相愛ですね！
It's mutual love, isn't it!
うん、相思相愛！
Yeah, mutual love!
But after that, that song, I am a little hungry.
What food do you like, Gura?
Hmm, I'm pretty hungry too. Mogu mogu mogu...
I really love salmon. What do you like?
Oh... I like fish, and shark fin, and...
Hehe... Okayu-senpai...
But I am so happy for you, Gura.
Congratulations, Same-chan!
あ、ありがとう、おかゆ先輩！
Ah, thank you, Okayu-senpai!
I'm so happy to have a chance to sing with you.
It was fun singing with you.
Let's sing together again soon.
Yes!
Oh no, there's no more time. I'm leaving. Bye!
No, no, no! ちょっと待って！
No, no, no! Wait a minute!
Okayu! Wait! Can I pet your tail? Okayu-senpai!
チチをもげ！
Grope the Breasts!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Tits, tits, tits, breasts
ぼいんぼい～ん (ぼいんぼい～ん)
Boing boing (Boing boing)
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Tits, tits, tits, breasts
ぼいんぼい～ん (ぼいんぼい～ん)
Boing boing (Boing boing)
もげ もげ もげ Uh Wao
Grope, grope, grope, Uh Wow
もげもげもげ チチをもげ
Grope, grope, grope, grope the breasts
もげぷいんぼよもげ
Grope, boing, boing, grope
もげぽらろんぷよもげ
まんまるチチ 三角おっぱい
Perfectly round tits, triangular breasts
ロケットボイン
Rocket boing
優しくもげ！
Grope gently!
いきなりもげ！
Grope suddenly!
微妙にもげ！
Grope subtly!
連続もげ！
Grope repeatedly!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Tits, tits, tits, breasts
ぼいんぼい～ん (ぼいんぼい～ん)
Boing boing (Boing boing)
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Tits, tits, tits, breasts
ぼいんぼい～ん (ぼいんぼい～ん)
Boing boing (Boing boing)
もげもげもげ チチをもげ もげ！
Grope, grope, grope, grope the breasts, grope!
もげもげもげ チチをもげ
Grope, grope, grope, grope the breasts
もげぽよいんぼよもげ
Grope, boing, boing, grope
もげぱいんぼいんもげ
しましまチチ おさるのおっぱい
Striped tits, monkey breasts
バズーカボイン
Bazooka boing
今日ももげ！
Grope today too!
明日ももげ！
Grope tomorrow too!
とにかくもげ！
Just grope!
毎日もげ！
Grope every day!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Tits, tits, tits, breasts
ぼいんぼい～ん (ぼいんぼい～ん)
Boing boing (Boing boing)
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Tits, tits, tits, breasts
ぼいんぼい～ん (ぼいんぼい～ん)
Boing boing (Boing boing)
もげもげもげ チチをもげ もげ！
Grope, grope, grope, grope the breasts, grope!
待て待て待て！
Wait wait wait!
捕まえてごらん！
Catch me if you can!
あー、よしよし。捕まえた！
Ah, there there. Caught you!
いやーん、そこはボインよ！
No way, that's my boing!
シオンぺったん！
Shion's flat!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Tits, tits, tits, breasts
ぼいんぼい～ん (ぼいんぼい～ん)
Boing boing (Boing boing)
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Tits, tits, tits, breasts
ぼいんぼい～ん (ぼいんぼい～ん)
Boing boing (Boing boing)
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Tits, tits, tits, breasts
ぼいんぼい～ん (ぼいんぼい～ん)
Boing boing (Boing boing)
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Tits, tits, tits, breasts
ぼいんぼい～ん (ぼいんぼい～ん)
Boing boing (Boing boing)
もげもげもげ チチをもげ！
Grope, grope, grope, grope the breasts!
もげ！もげ！もげ！もげ！ チチをもげ
Grope! Grope! Grope! Grope! Grope the breasts
Uh Moge!
シオン、まったねー！
Shion, see you later!
Thank you for coming.
ぐらー！来たよー！
Gura! I'm here!
We can sing together again.
うん、呼んでくれてありがとう。
Mm, thanks for inviting me.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
シオンのライブにも来てくれたよね。
You came to my live too, didn't you?
Oh, that was so much fun!
I'm glad we got to sing together again here today.
Me too.
でも本当に暑いね。
But it's really hot, isn't it?
Hot.
It's very hot, isn't it?
Rather sticky.
But it is summer, so I guess that makes sense.
Oh, speaking of summer, do you like eating melon?
I like big watermelons.
They're so juicy and delicious.
ねえぐら。 ま、まく...
Hey Gura. W-wait...
何か言いたいことでもあるの？
Is there something you want to say?
Um... but summer is nice.
I like the beach and eating watermelon too.
あ、シオンは泳ぐことができますか？
Ah, Shion, can you swim?
できるよ。
I can.
ほう！
Hoh!
じゃ、今度アトランティスに一緒に行こう！
Then, let's go to Atlantis together next time!
えええー！？
Ehh!?
No way!
それは無理！
That's impossible!
息がそんなに持たないよ。
I can't hold my breath that long.
いや大丈夫大丈夫。
No, it's okay, it's okay.
I will help.
じゃ、考えておく。
Then, I'll think about it.
はい。
Yes.
Okay, it's a promise.
But now it's time for the next song.
Thank you Shion.
Bye bye Gura!
Bye bye!
Tricolore Airline
Artist: Hatsune Miku
Composer: otsuzukun
Lyrics: otsuzukun
今夜 空港で待ってて",
Wait for me at the airport tonight
黄昏の空に浮かぶ",
Floating in the twilight sky
金星のすぐそばで",
Right next to Venus
ねぇ いつか 蒼い成層圏へ",
Hey, someday into the blue stratosphere
二人きりどこまでも飛べるかな",
I wonder if we can fly anywhere together
夜の雲海越え 1000マイル彼方へと",
Crossing the sea of clouds, 1000 miles away
旅客飛行を",
On a passenger flight
あなただけの アテンダントの私",
Your very own attendant, me
トリコロール・エアライン",
Tricolore Airline
はるか 異国の空かな",
Far away, in a foreign sky
甘いあなたに贈る",
Sending to you, my sweetheart
絵葉書 恋のエアメール",
A postcard, airmail of love
あぁ 私 ひとり窓辺で",
Ah, I am alone by the window
夕立の輝きがまぶしい",
The brilliance of the evening shower is dazzling
夜の雲海越え 1000マイル彼方へと",
Crossing the sea of clouds, 1000 miles away
旅客飛行を",
On a passenger flight
あなただけの アテンダントの私",
Your very own attendant, me
トリコロール・エアライン",
Tricolore Airline
夜の雲海越え 1000マイル彼方へと",
Crossing the sea of clouds, 1000 miles away
旅客飛行を",
On a passenger flight
あなただけの アテンダントの私",
Your very own attendant, me
トリコロール・エアライン",
Tricolore Airline
あ、ぐら！400万登録おめでとう！
Ah, Gura! 4 million subscribers, congratulations!
ほ、ありがとう！
Ho, thank you!
Oh, you are famous shark.
Oh, you are a famous shark.
あー。
Ah.
本当におめでとう、すごいね！
Truly, congratulations. That's amazing!
あー、ありがとう。
Ah, thank you.
あくあ先輩、マリン先輩、thank you for coming.
Aqua-senpai, Marine-senpai, thank you for coming.
I'm so excited we can sing together again.
I'm kind of nervous...
...like I can't control my heart, it's beating very, very rapidly. ドキドキドキドキ。
...like I can't control my heart, it's beating very, very rapidly. Doki-doki-doki-doki.
マリンとあくあはどうですか？
How about you, Marine and Aqua?
Me too, doki-doki.
Gura, it was my dream to sing on stage with you.
So, I am really happy.
Please sing at my next live too.
Really? I would be honored, Marine.
私もソロライブの時はまだ3Dじゃなかったから...
Back during my solo live, I didn't have a 3D model yet...
...3Dで一緒に歌えて嬉しい。
...so I'm happy we can sing together in 3D.
Yeah!
あー、ぐら、ぐら。
Ah, Gura, Gura.
Can I ask a favor?
ふん... I want to be eaten by you, Gura.
Hum... I want to be eaten by you, Gura.
It depends on what you taste like.
どんな味だろう？
I wonder what you taste like?
Dangerous Marine smell.
Recent? やべー。
Recent? Oh boy.
I hope we have more opportunities to perform together soon.
Sure! Please invite me anytime.
いいね！
That sounds good!
Thank you guys for coming today.
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Gura, congratulations!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Bye-bye!
My Soul, Your Beats!
目覚めては繰り返す
Awakening, it repeats
眠い朝は
These sleepy mornings
襟のタイを
Tightening the tie
きつく締め
At my collar
教室のドアくぐると
When I pass through the classroom door
ほんの少し
I puff out my chest
胸を張って
Just a little bit
歩き出せる
And I can start walking
そんな日常に
In that everyday life
吹き抜ける風
The wind blowing through
聞こえた気がした
I felt like I heard it
感じた気がしたんだ
I felt like I could feel it
震え出す
Starting to tremble
今この胸で
Right now, in this heart
もう来る気がした
I felt like it was already coming
幾億の星が
Billions of stars
消えていくのを
Watching them
見送った
As they disappear
手を振った
I waved my hand
よかったね、と
Saying, 'I'm glad'
廊下の隅見下ろす
Looking down from the corner of the hallway
掃除の途中
While I was cleaning
おかしなもの
I think it's
だと思う
A strange thing
あたしの中の時間は
Even though time inside of me
止まってるのに
Has stopped
違う日々を
As if I'm living
生きてるように
Through different days
埃は雪の
The dust piles up
ように降り積む
Like snow
待ってる気がした
I felt like I was waiting
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I felt like I was being called
震え出す
Starting to tremble
今この時が見つけた気がした
I felt like I found this moment right now
失われた記憶が
Memories that were lost
呼び覚ました
Have been awakened
物語
A story
永遠の
Of an eternal
その終わり
Conclusion
いつの間にか
Before I knew it
駆け出してた
I started running
あなたに手を
To your hand
目覚めてきた...
I woke up...
昨日は遠く
Yesterday is far away
明日はすぐ
Tomorrow is coming soon
そんな当たり前に
In such a natural way
心が躍った
My heart leaped
聞こえた気がした 感じた気がしたんだ
I felt like I heard it, I felt like I sensed it
震えだす 今この胸で
Starting to tremble, now in this chest
もう来る気がした
I felt it was already coming
幾千万の朝を越え
Crossing through millions of mornings
新しい陽が
A new sun
待ってる気がした
I felt like it was waiting
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I felt like it was calling out
震えてるこの魂が
This trembling soul
見つけた気がした
I felt like I found it
幾億の夢のように
Like hundreds of millions of dreams
消え去る日を
The day it disappears
見送った
I saw it off
手を振った
I waved my hand
ありがとうと
Saying thank you
Kronk! Kronnichiwa!
Domo, Shammidesshu.
Yah yah yah! Domo, Shammidesshu.
Is that what I really sound like?
Yes, you do.
Um... okay...
I've done some improvising, but still...
I was expecting a little...
I was expecting a little bit of hesitation, but I guess...
Oh, improvising, so you're adding to it.
Yes. Shammidesshu. Shammidesshu. Oh! Ooh!
Thank you for...
Alright!
Thanks for coming and singing with me today, Kronii.
Oh, no, thank you!
Thank you!
You're looking mighty magnificent in your...
...how would I say...
...cardboard.
Cardboard.
Still taller than you though.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, like you need some growing up to do, literally.
Hey! You're like 95% legs, okay?
But you came out like that. All legs.
95% legs, 5%... okay, you don't have to go that hard.
Anyway.
Okay, spider-cat!
Woah!
Oh my god!
My feelings!
What are you going to do with those weapons? Shish-kebab me?
Uh... it's not worth it.
But your shrimp friends over there look pretty tasty.
I might skewer them.
Ay, leave some for me if you do.
Say though...
How do I... what do I...
...compost or recycle you right now?
Uh, well, you can't.
Uh, you gotta add me... uh, to the Kronii Temple.
Kind of add it as a limited edition kind of thing.
Right, right, mhm.
Well, what if I just hoist you right here?
Wait, what? Wait, what? Wait...
And I take you to whatever I find first. Compost? Recycle?
Maybe I'll just put you in my room.
Dah-dah-dah-dah-dah...
Wait!
ピョン ピョン ピョン ピョン ピョン ピョン!
Pyon pyon pyon pyon pyon pyon!
皆さん、ありがとうございます！
Everyone, thank you so much!
Thank you guys for watching!
I hope you enjoyed what we prepared for you!
Thank you to my wonderful senpai for singing with me...
...and Kroni-shuki Shammidesshu.
Ah, I felt tears welling in my eyes every day I practiced for today.
This concert has been one of my dreams come true...
...and it's all possible thanks to each and every one of you.
最初からサポートしてくれてありがとうございます。
Thank you for supporting me from the beginning.
Hololive English, Gawr Guraでした！
It was Gawr Gura from Hololive English!
そばにいられて...
Being by your side...
みんなの前で踊ったり歌ったりできた夢みたいです。
being able to dance and sing in front of everyone, it feels like a dream.
またいつかみんなの前でライブに立ちたいです。
I want to stand on the live stage in front of everyone again someday.
その日まで目を閉じてみんなの素敵な顔を想像します。
Until that day, I'll close my eyes and imagine all of your wonderful faces.
Now,
one more song before we end today.
いくよー！
Here we go!
好きになって！もっと！
Love me! More!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me! More!
恩返しは...
My payback is...
愛のこもった投げキッスで
with a blown kiss full of love
気のせいじゃない
It's not your imagination
目は合ってるよ
Our eyes are meeting
あとちょっとで
Just a little more
恋しちゃってください
Please fall in love with me
やれること
The things I can do
何でもします
I'll do anything
NGなしで
With no "No-Go's"
体当たり挑戦
Trying my best with everything
エゴサで見つけたアンチのコメも
Even the anti-comments I found while searching myself
ぶっちゃけみんなより分かってるし
To be honest, I know them better than anyone
でも大丈夫　ここに立てば
But it's okay, if I stand here
みんながいる
Everyone is here
いくよ！
Here we go!
好きになって！もっと！
Love me! More!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me! More!
恩返しは...
My payback is...
愛のこもった投げキッスで
with a blown kiss full of love
虜にする！もっと！
I'll captivate you! More!
夢を見せる！もっと！
I'll show you dreams! More!
楽しんでって
Enjoy yourself
愛のこもったスペシャルナイト
A special night full of love
ファンサしちゃうぞ(・ω＜)
I'm gonna give you some fan service! (・ω＜)
みんな！ありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you!
お手紙も書いてください
Please write me letters too
何度も読んで宝物にします
I'll read them over and over and treasure them
卒業だなんてまだ早いけど
It's too early to talk about graduation
裏切りません
I won't betray you
宣言しときます
I'll declare it now
口先だけじゃ説得力ない
Lip service isn't persuasive
ぶっちゃけ実力で勝ってやる
To be honest, I'll win with my own skills
だからやめない　負けず嫌い
So I won't quit, I hate to lose
私はいる
I am here
いくよ！
Here we go!
拳上げて！もっと！
Raise your fists! More!
汗をかいて！もっと！
Work up a sweat! More!
恩返しは...
My payback is...
愛のこもったサメビームで
with a shark beam full of love
大歓声！もっと！
Loud cheers! More!
まだまだだね？もっと！
Not enough yet, right? More!
受け止めてね
Please accept it
愛のこもったわがままソング
A selfish song full of love
ファンサしちゃうぞ(・ω＜)
I'm gonna give you some fan service! (・ω＜)
近づく寂しさに
To the loneliness drawing near...
楽しいのに泣きそうだよ
even though it's fun, I feel like crying
次も
Next time
次もまた会えるよね
we can meet again next time too, right?
約束！
Promise!
優しさに溢れている言葉
The words overflowing with kindness,
怒鳴り散らす誰かの言葉も
even the words of someone shouting,
必要なんだ　必要なんだ
they're necessary, they're necessary.
強くなろう
Let's become strong.
好きに叫べ！もっと！
Shout as you like! More!
楽しんじゃえ！もっと！
Just enjoy it! More!
忘れないで
Don't forget,
特別な日になりますように
may it be a special day.
共に歌おう　ずっと！
Let's sing together, forever!
共に歩もう　ずっと！
Let's walk together, forever!
合言葉はとびっきりの
The password is the best
L・O・V・E
好きになって！もっと！
Love me! More!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me! More!
恩返しは...
My payback is...
愛のこもった投げキッスで
with a blown kiss full of love
虜にする！もっと！
I'll captivate you! More!
夢を見せる！もっと！
I'll show you dreams! More!
楽しんでって
Enjoy yourself
愛のこもったスペシャルナイト
A special night full of love
ファンサしちゃうぞ(・ω＜)
I'm gonna give you some fan service! (・ω＜)
Gawr Gura 4 Million Subscribers Celebration Merchandise Coming Soon!!!
Gawr Gura
4 Million Subscribers Celebration Merchandise
Coming Soon!!!
Thank you for watching!